(Sheldon:)You're clearly listed
as founder.
(Leonard:)Well, yes, and you're listed
(Leonard:)as Chief Executive Officer,
(Leonard:)Chief Financial Officer
and Chief Operating Officer.
(Sheldon:)You missed
Chief Science Officer,
(Sheldon:)Chairman of the Board, and Head
of the Secret Santa Committee.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)You need to get clear
on this right now.
(Leonard:)I am in charge of this project.
(Raj:)Ooh. Leonard's going all
alpha nerd on Sheldon's ass...
(Sheldon:)All right. All right,
I'm not going to argue with you.
(Sheldon:)Sheldon Cooper is nothing
if not a team player.
(Sheldon:)Dr. Hofstadter,
you have the conn.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)I thought we might start
(Leonard:)by talking
about the user interface.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord, we're doomed.
(Leonard:)So this button here
(Leonard:)will allow you
to scan a new equation,
(Leonard:)but over here,
you can press this,
(Leonard:)and just substitute new values
for the coefficients.
(Sheldon:)Good one, boss.
(Raj(pressing button on camera phone. Camera makes a fart noise):)What?
(Sheldon:)This diagram.